8 consecutive correct answers system is seriously debilitating.
I have decided
Is Mr. Ichikawa the second one to get it right?
Impossible.
Moe Kachan, here she is.
So cute!
We've decided on Ira!
This is Ira.
Oh, wow!
Looks like her.
Hana-chan, you're looking pretty good.
Okay.
Open your eyes, please.
This way, please.
Wow!
I woke up too.
When I put them all together...
Oh, is this Hana-san?
The three of us... Oh, this is all we have.
Done?
Done.
This way.
Wow!
There's so many!
Well then, I'd like to meet with you one more time and work on the cat's mensch.
So take good care of it.
I couldn't get my teeth into it.
I couldn't get into this intense group.
I couldn't join the group.I couldn't get into the group.
But it's intense.
Yeah.
I couldn't hide my teeth.
Oh, but...
I can hear everything you're doing.
Pretty for you
My line
Me, me, me
If it's words, I don't need them anymore
ana ana ana, I'll go first, then you...
But you know... there's always the last day
I want to be in the center, so I want to be in the middle
Now let's go to this girl...
I'm very steady... if you look for your own point of view...
I'm the one who says I'm the one who does everything, after all...
I'm a dentist.
ana No!
I guess it was.
I want to be the center, so I'm going to work hard.
I don't want to be the center of Mo-chan's group...
But maybe she wants to be the center... maybe she wants to be the center.
Then let's do it!
I want to go home even if I don't think about it.
You...
You
2, your position
Let's do it!
Ha-ha-ha-ha
Cut out all of this here, everyone.I want you all to cut all of this out and put it on TikTok.
stream it to TikTok!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, pull yourselves together.
No, no, no.
So you're saying we should just do a self-pull?
Oh, self-pull.
Self-pull.
I'll do a "self-draw".
I'm in the back.
I'm coming out.
I want to go home.
I really want to go home.
Oh, shit.
I want to go home.
Concentrate, please.
I want to go home to the warmth of my home.
I wanna go home
I want to go home
I want to go home.
Home is warm
Yes!
No!
That's not good at all.It's not good at all.
Is it bad?
Why not? Oh, man.
It's not good.
I can't see a way out.
I'm taking all of this.
No, no, no, no.
There's gonna be a lot of it, isn't there?
Oh, my God.
My bangs, sicher.
It'll only happen once.
So, Suzuki, who has become Ayaka, is out.
She's a sensitive woman.
That's okay.
I'm Terrace.
I'm a sensitive woman who can notice many things.
So, Mr. Suzuki, you're home!
Thank you for your hard work!
Thank you very much!
Is it okay?
I'm still feeling down about this, even if you say it's you.
Bye-bye, I'm going home.
Bye, bye, bye.
Let's do it.
Let's do it!
Okay, I'm going.
I'm going.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no
yes no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
smile
heh heh heh
eh eh
(smile)
Ah
smile
LOL
Thank you for your hard work.
I knew it!
I don't have anything to spare.
ohhhhhhhhhh!
thank you for all your hard work
Thank you for your hard work
Bye-bye, yes, bye-bye
Okay, come on, be a little more frustrated
Thank you for your hard work
Ending
Oh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh!
It's going to be fun!
But which one of us is going to come back with you when you're done?
Yeah, I don't really care which way we go!
Sure!Yes, indeed!
Oh no, 5 minutes is approaching!
Oh!
Good job!
Wait a minute, engine.
Good work, guys!
Wait a minute.
What are you talking about? We're just going home.
Thank you for your hard work! Thank you very much!
I'm just going to take this one quick shot and then I'll be on my way.
I'm going!
Cow.
There is such a thing as practice.
I'm going.
I might not have enough time, so I'm going to use this to get some scale.
It's great to be able to talk with you all even through the screen like this.
I don't have any plans or anything.
I'm busy over there.
It's done! It's done!
It's all here!
We did it!
I thought I'd never get it right.
Please don't fast forward or anything.
I've been doing this forever.
It was so much fun! Thank you so much!
Don Carbon...
I don't want it.
Well, thank you for your time!